{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"80.1/0.9",
			"answer":"80.1/0.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.04/0.003",
			"answer":"2.04/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.672/0.6",
			"answer":"0.672/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.34/0.02",
			"answer":"3.34/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"82.6/0.2",
			"answer":"82.6/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.775/0.005",
			"answer":"0.775/0.005",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"55.8/0.9",
			"answer":"55.8/0.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.16/0.06",
			"answer":"2.16/0.06",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"93.6/9",
			"answer":"93.6/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"17.5/0.7",
			"answer":"17.5/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}